Nope, I don't have it
I don't have it
I should have
his number as a friend
But I don't have it
Il-tak!
I have
to get that number
What?
Number?
Did you get
a girlfriend?
What the hell?
That's weird
You don't have
an ounce of manliness
but you managed
to get a girl?
Who is this bitch?
What are you on about?
It's a guy
Mom!
Il-tak has a boyfriend!
Hey! You crazy little…
So
you want to get close
to this guy?
Face it, Il-tak
That's love
Can you shut the hell up?
Forget it
I'm an idiot
for asking you
You sure?
I'm really popular
at school
You?
Look at this
All these guys asked
for my number
[Can I call you?]
[Can I come
to your class tomorrow?]
[You free tomorrow?]
[Text me back]
What the hell?
It's true
What did I tell you?
Will you listen
to me now?
Give me the briefing
I can't give Il-tak away
to just anyone